Guide to the Lester R. Armstrong Photographs circa 1917-1957
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Heater, Nobel and Winifred, 1946 August 2 (Box 2, Folder 693)
- Heater, Rem, 1944 November (Box 2, Folder 691)
- Heater, Rem, 1948 April 8 (Box 2, Folder 698)
- Heater, Theora, 1951 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 694)
- Heater, Theora, 1952 April 18 (Box 2, Folder 695)
- Heater, Theora, 1951 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 696)
- Heater: Girls, 1952 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 697)
- Heceta Head, Oregon, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1800)
- Heimbigner, 1943 October (Box 2, Folder 705)
- Heimbigner, 1943 November (Box 2, Folder 706)
- Heimbigner, 1944 April (Box 2, Folder 708)
- Heimbigner, 1944 October (Box 2, Folder 709)
- Heimbigner, 44168 (Box 2, Folder 710)
- Heimbigner, 1944 February (Box 2, Folder 699)
- Heimbigner, Anniversary party, 1945 September (Box 2, Folder 707)
- Heimbigner, Jo Ann, 1946 July (Box 2, Folder 704)
- Heimbigner, Jo Ann: Birthday party, Undated (Box 2, Folder 700)
- Heimbigner: Birthday Party: Jo Ann, Circa 1945 (Box 2, Folder 701)
- Heimbigner: Family Group, Circa 1946 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Heimbigner: Family: Group, 1943 December (Box 2, Folder 702)
- Heimbigner: Fiftieth Anniversary, 1945 January (Box 2, Folder 703)
- Heiser, Ruby, 1950 August (Box 2, Folder 711)
- Heiser, Ruby, Circa 1950 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Heiser: Portrait: Grandmother, 1950 August 15 (Box 2, Folder 712)
- Hemlock, C. E.: Baby, 1948 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 713)
- Hemp, Pete, 1948 January 27 (Box 2, Folder 714)
- Hereford: Fifth Annual Auction Sale, 1950 March 6 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Hereford: Fourth Annual Auction Sale, Circa 1949 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Herford: Polled: Show and sale, 1949 March 7 (Box 2, Folder 715)
- Herford: Sale: Walla Walla, 43889 (Box 2, Folder 716)
- Herford: Show and sale: Walla Walla fairgrounds, 1948 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 717)
- Herring, Sargeant, 1943 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 718)
- Hetters, Gill: Depoe Bay: Fishing dock, Circa 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1813)
- High school dance, Undated (Box 2, Folder 397)
- High School girls [African American], Undated (Box 2, Folder 719)
- Highway accident: Swartz, Donald, 43920 (Box 2, Folder 720)
- Highway loop, Undated (Box 2, Folder 721)
- Highways, Undated (Box 2, Folder 723)
- Hill, Bill, Undated (Box 2, Folder 725)
- Hill, Bill: horses, Circa 1948 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Hill, Bill: Planting Bulbs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 726)
- Hill, Bill: Saddle Horse, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 724)
- Hill, Luciel: Majorette: Walla Walla Drum Corps, Circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 727)
- Hirsch, Dina, Undated (Box 2, Folder 728)
- Hirsch, Dina, Undated (Box 2, Folder 729)
- Hirsch, Leid: Boy: Mrs. Pat, 1949 November 28 (Box 2, Folder 730)
- Hirsch: Baby, 1950 April 15 (Box 2, Folder 733)
- Hirsch: Baby, 1948 November 7 (Box 2, Folder 735)
- Hirsch: Boy, 1950 April 16 (Box 2, Folder 732)
- Hirsch: Copy, 1948 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 731)
- Hirsch: Mary, 1949 March 4 (Box 2, Folder 734)
- Hogan: Plasterer, Undated (Box 2, Folder 736)
- Holm, Ransom: Bus truck, Undated (Box 2, Folder 737)
- Holmes, Oliver: Party, etcetera, Undated (Box 2, Folder 738)
- Holmwood, Wanda, Undated (Box 2, Folder 739)
- Hood, Mountain, Undated (Box 2, Folder 740)
- Hooper Furniture Comapany store, Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Hooper Furniture Company, 1942 May (Box 2, Folder 741)
- Hopfield, Undated (Box 2, Folder 742)
- Hops, Undated (Box 2, Folder 743)
- Hornet Nest: Priest Lake, 1949 July (Box 2, Folder 744)
- Horse, Undated (Box 2, Folder 746)
- Horse Race, Undated (Box 2, Folder 745)
- Horse races: Dayton, 1942 May (Box 2, Folder 750)
- Horse Races: Walla Walla, 1942 May (Box 2, Folder 747)
- Horse races: Walla Walla, 1942 May (Box 2, Folder 751)
- Horse: Mare and Colt, Undated (Box 2, Folder 748)
- Horse: Race: Dr. Milne, Undated (Box 2, Folder 749)
- Horses, Undated (Box 2, Folder 753)
- Horses bucking: Dayton, 1942 May (Box 2, Folder 752)
- Horses: Bergevin, Walla Walla County Fair, Circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 754)
- Hortin, Shirley, 1951 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 755)
- Hortin, Shirley, 1950 February 13 (Box 2, Folder 756)
- Hospital, Undated (Box 2, Folder 757)
- Hospital: Patients, Undated (Box 2, Folder 787)
- Hospital: Personnel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 788)
- Hospital: Soap Lake, Undated (Box 2, Folder 789)
- Hospital: United States Veterans Hospital, San Francisco: Fort Miley, Circa 1933 (Box 2, Folder 790)
- Hospital: Veterans, 1946 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 792)
- Hospital: Veterans: Patients, Circa 1920 (Box 2, Folder 791)
- House mover, 1947 April 4 (Box 2, Folder 793)
- House mover, 1947 March 12 (Box 2, Folder 794)
- House moving, 1946 October 12 (Box 2, Folder 795)
- Hoy, Mr. and Mrs., Undated (Box 2, Folder 796)
- Huie, Clara, 1948 November 11 (Box 2, Folder 797)
- Huie, Clara and Mary Smith, 1948 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 798)
- Huie, Fanny: Chinese, Undated (Box 2, Folder 799)
- Hull, Undated (Box 2, Folder 800)
- Hulse, Mr. and Mrs., 1953 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 801)
- Hunter: Residence, 1948 November 12 (Box 2, Folder 803)
- Hunter: Wedding anniversary, 1948 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 802)
- Hunter: Wedding anniversary, 1948 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 804)
- Huntington, J. B., Undated (Box 2, Folder 806)
- Huntington, J. B.: Fern and Vine, 1947 July 27 (Box 2, Folder 805)
- Huntington, Jack: Children, 1949 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 807)
- Hurst, Mary, 1948 January 8 (Box 2, Folder 808)
- Hurst, Mary, 1948 September 30 (Box 2, Folder 809)
- Hutchinson, Miss Bonnie: Route 1: Raymond, Washington, Undated (Box 2, Folder 810)
- Inas: Girl, Circa 1949 (Box 3, Folder 811)
- Indian Girls: Celilo: Toontot, Edna: Synthia Switzer, Undated (Box 3, Folder 813)
- Indian Girls: La Push, Washington: Pauline Eastman, 1949 August (Box 3, Folder 812)
- Indian Horses: Walla Walla County Fair: Luke Cowapoo, Undated (Box 3, Folder 814)
- Indian papoose: Virginia Minthorn: Mission, Oregon, 1949 September (Box 3, Folder 815)
- Indian Pow Wow: Lewiston, Idaho, 1944 May (Box 3, Folder 817)
- Indian rock writing: Near McNary Dam, found by engineers, Circa 1953 (Box 3, Folder 819)
- Indian rock writing: Page, Washington, 1949 October (Box 3, Folder 818)
- Indian Writing: Port Kelly, Washington, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Indian Writing: Sheffler Station, Washington, 1949 September (Box 3, Folder 820)
- Indian Writings: Vantage, Washington, 1949 July (Box 3, Folder 821)
- Indians: Peter Bones, Undated (Box 3, Folder 816)
- Indians: Fishing at Celilo, Circa 1949 (Box 3, Folder 825)
- Indians: Hop yards, Hermiston, Circa 1935 (Box 3, Folder 826)
- Indians: La Push, Undated (Box 3, Folder 822)
- Indians: Umatilla, Undated (Box 3, Folder 827)
- Indians: Walla Walla County Fair, Undated (Box 3, Folder 824)
- Indians: Walla Walla: Rodeo, 1945 September 1 (Box 3, Folder 823)
- Industrial and factory, Undated (Box 3, Folder 828)
- Industrial: Coca-Cola, Undated (Box 3, Folder 829)
- Industrial: Farming, Undated (Box 3, Folder 830)
- Industrial: Grain Elevators, Undated (Box 3, Folder 831)
- Industrial: Painting, Undated (Box 3, Folder 832)
- Industrial: Utility, Undated (Box 3, Folder 833)
- Infrared: view from Mormon grade, Undated (Box 3, Folder 834)
- Inland Empire Pioneer Association, 1947 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 835)
- Inland Excavating company: Sewer Contract, 1948 September (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Interior: Home, Undated (Box 3, Folder 836)
- Interior: Metropolitan stores, opening day, Undated (Box 3, Folder 837)
- Interstate Metals, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Interstate Metals Incorporated, 1947 September 18 (Box 3, Folder 838)
- Iris, Show, 1948 June 3 (Box 3, Folder 841)
- Iris: Glads, Undated (Box 3, Folder 842)
- Iron: Scrap drive, Circa 1942 (Box 3, Folder 843)
- Irwin, Gladys, 1948 March 22 (Box 3, Folder 839)
- Irwin, Lieutenant Gladys, 1943 September 20 (Box 3, Folder 840)
- Isitt, Benny and Family, 1952 December 4 (Box 3, Folder 844)
- Jaffee, Undated (Box 3, Folder 845)
- Jaffee, 1945 December 28 (Box 3, Folder 846)
- Jaffee, Doctor, 1946 June 10 (Box 3, Folder 848)
- Jaffee, Maj., Undated (Box 3, Folder 847)
- Jameson, Doctor, 1946 March 24 (Box 3, Folder 849)
- Japanese girl, Undated (Box 3, Folder 850)
- Jaynes: Typewriter, Undated (Box 3, Folder 860)
- Jensen, Val, 1946 August 21 (Box 3, Folder 851)
- Johanesson, Doctor, 1947 January 18 (Box 3, Folder 852)
- Johannesson, Dr. C. F: X- Ray Lab, Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
- John Day trip, 44024 (Box 3, Folder 853)
- Johnson, Mrs. Doris, Undated (Box 3, Folder 854)
- Johnson, LaVerne: With sister-in-law, 1952 August 3 (Box 3, Folder 855)
- Johnson, Lowden, 1946 August 21 (Box 3, Folder 856)
- Johnson: Ella, Mae, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1523)
- Junior chamber: Banquet, 1947 June 27 (Box 3, Folder 857)
- Junk: Aviation wreckage, Undated (Box 3, Folder 858)
- Justice, Mrs., 1949 March (Box 3, Folder 859)
- Keith, Undated (Box 3, Folder 861)
- Keith, Sandra, 1952 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 862)
- Keith, Sandra, 1952 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 863)
- Kent, Sergeant and Family, Undated (Box 3, Folder 864)
- Kight, Mel, Undated (Box 3, Folder 865)
- Kirkpatrick, J.G family group, 1948 December 25 (Box 3, Folder 866)
- Kirkpatrick, Miss paper girl, 1948 December 21 (Box 3, Folder 867)
- Kirschner, H.J.: Daughter on beach, Undated (Box 3, Folder 868)
- Kitchen Sink, Undated (Box 3, Folder 870)
- Knifong, Harvey, 1950 March 11 (Box 3, Folder 869)
- Knight, Undated (Box 3, Folder 871)
- Knight, 1945 March 29 (Box 3, Folder 873)
- Knight, 1948 January 17 (Box 3, Folder 878)
- Knight, 1948 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 879)
- Knight, Margaret, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Knight, Margaret: D. Service, 1948 January 2 (Box 3, Folder 875)
- Knight, Mrs., 1948 January 4 (Box 3, Folder 876)
- Knight, Mrs., 1948 December 11 (Box 3, Folder 877)
- Knight: Best of all, Undated (Box 3, Folder 872)
- Knight: Best of all, Undated (Box 3, Folder 874)
- Kooskooskie, Undated (Box 3, Folder 880)
- Kroni, 1945 December 6 (Box 3, Folder 881)
- Kyle, Undated (Box 3, Folder 882)
- La Push: Docks and seascapes, 1949 August (Box 3, Folder 907)
- La Push: Fishing boats and harbor, Circa 1949 (Box 3, Folder 908)
- La Rue: Children, Circa 1948 (Box 3, Folder 909)
- Labor Camp, Mexican: Dixie, 1946 July (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Laboratory specimen, 1944 July 7 (Box 3, Folder 883)
- Lacy, 1946 October 22 (Box 3, Folder 886)
- Lacy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 884)
- Lacy, Earl: Family group, 1948 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 885)
- Lacy: Girls, 1951 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 887)
- Lake American, Undated (Box 3, Folder 888)
- Lake Chelan, Undated (Box 3, Folder 889)
- Lake, Park: Walla Walla, Undated (Box 3, Folder 896)
- Lake: City park: Walla Walla, 1944 July (Box 3, Folder 890)
- Lake: Coeur D'Alene, Undated (Box 3, Folder 891)
- Lake: Crescent, Circa 1949 (Box 3, Folder 892)
- Lake: Eastlake, Oregon, Undated (Box 3, Folder 893)
- Lake: Ketchess, Undated (Box 3, Folder 894)
- Lake: Langdon, Undated (Box 3, Folder 895)
- Lake: Park, Undated (Box 3, Folder 897)
- Lake: Priest, 1949 July (Box 3, Folder 898)
- Lake: Soap Lake, 1949 July (Box 3, Folder 900)
- Lake: Soap Lake, Undated (Box 3, Folder 899)
- Lake: Wallowa, Undated (Box 3, Folder 901)
- Lake: Wenatchee, Undated (Box 3, Folder 902)
- Lamm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 904)
- Lamm, Loretta, 1944 February (Box 3, Folder 903)
- Land, Ray, 1948 December 21 (Box 3, Folder 905)
- Land, Ray, 1949 September (Box 3, Folder 906)
- Laundry, Circa 1948 (Box 3, Folder 910)
- Lava Butte: Information Board, 1952 August (Box 3, Folder 911)
- Le Roux, Frank, 1940 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 920)
- Le Roux, Frank, 1940 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 921)
- Leach Children, 1949 December 25 (Box 3, Folder 912)
- Leach, James F., 1946 December 25 (Box 3, Folder 913)
- Leach, James F.: McCaw, Undated (Box 3, Folder 914)
- Leach, James F.: McCaw housing project, 1947 December 25 (Box 3, Folder 917)
- Leading Fur Shop, 1946 October 27 (Box 3, Folder 915)
- Leaf: Growing and sprouting, Undated (Box 3, Folder 916)
- Legs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 918)
- Lenore, Idaho, 1943 October 5 (Box 3, Folder 919)
- Letterheads, stationary, Undated (Box 3, Folder 922)
- Levens, Clarence: Baby, 1947 November 14 (Box 3, Folder 923)
- Lewis, Zeb, 1950 March 6 (Box 3, Folder 924)
- Ley, Undated (Box 3, Folder 925)
- Liberty pool hall, 1946 September 31 (Box 3, Folder 926)
- Life Magazine: Photographer, Undated (Box 3, Folder 927)
- Lightfoot, Mrs. Juanita, 1949 October 13 (Box 3, Folder 928)
- Lighthouse and vicinity: Coos Bay, Oregon, Undated (Box 3, Folder 929)
- Lights, Carnival, Undated (Box 3, Folder 930)
- Lincoln Rock, Undated (Box 3, Folder 933)
- Lincoln, Irma, 1948 October 24 (Box 3, Folder 931)
- LIncoln, Miss, 1947 February 2 (Box 3, Folder 932)
- Linotype, Walla Walla, Undated (Box 3, Folder 934)
- Lioy, Captain Anthony D., Undated (Box 3, Folder 936)
- Lioy, Doctor, Undated (Box 3, Folder 935)
- Livestock, Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Locks: Lake Union, Undated (Box 3, Folder 937)
- Locomotive, Undated (Box 3, Folder 938)
- Log petrified at Vantage, 1940 January (Box 3, Folder 940)
- Logging, Undated (Box 3, Folder 941)
- Logging near Portland, Undated (Box 3, Folder 942)
- Logging: Yarding in Olympic Peninsula, Undated (Box 3, Folder 943)
- Long, Mrs., Undated (Box 3, Folder 944)
- Lot corner: Locust and Division street, Undated (Box 3, Folder 945)
- Lot vacant: Locust and Division street, 1948 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 946)
- Low Tide, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1791)
- Lowana, Piper: Billy, Clarkson, 1946 August 10 (Box 4, Folder 1227)
- Lowden, John, 1951 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 947)
- Lowden: St. Mary's Nursery, 1946 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 948)
- Lumber camp and mill: Craig Mount Lumber Company, Circa 1917 (Box 3, Folder 949)
- Lumber Company, Tum-A-Lum, Undated (Box 3, Folder 950)
- Lyall, Drake, 1941 March (Box 2, Folder 443)
- Lynch, Undated (Box 3, Folder 951)
- Lynch, Emmell: Ranch: 9 mile: Walla Walla County, Circa 1948 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Lynch, Emmit, 1948 February 7 (Box 3, Folder 954)
- Lynch, Emmit, 1946 March 18 (Box 3, Folder 955)
- Lynch, Emmit, Undated (Box 3, Folder 956)
- Lynch, Emmit, Undated (Box 3, Folder 957)
- Lynch, Emmit, Undated (Box 3, Folder 958)
- Lynch, Emmitt: Hereford herd, 1948 February 6 (Box 3, Folder 953)
- M. Mounce, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1075)
- Maber, Gerald: Family Group: Group Picture, 1948 February 1 (Box 3, Folder 1004)
- MacDoel, California, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1005)
- Mace, Dallas, 1946 October 26 (Box 3, Folder 1006)
- Maddison, Betty, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1008)
- Maddison, Betty, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1009)
- Maddison, Betty, Circa 1943 (Box 3, Folder 1010)
- Maddox, Frank, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1007)
- Madison, Robert, 1947 April 12 (Box 3, Folder 1011)
- Maestretti, Betty, 1948 October 25 (Box 3, Folder 1012)
- Maher, Gerald: Family Group, Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Mahon, Beauty Shop: Dorothy, 1948 February 8 (Box 3, Folder 1013)
- Majonniers Greenhouse, 1946 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 641)
- Manning, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1014)
- Manning, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1016)
- Manning, J. Whitney, 1942 March (Box 3, Folder 1015)
- Many Glacier: Glacier National Park, Montana, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1807)
- Marbaugh: Boy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1017)
- Marge, Grube, 1950 February 27 (Box 2, Folder 646)
- Marine: Ocean, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1018)
- Marine: Port of Seattle, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1019)
- Marine: Puget Sound; Fletcher's Bay, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1024)
- Marines: Beaches, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1022)
- Marines: Harbor views, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1023)
- Marines: United States: Traveling arms display, 1951 August (Box 3, Folder 1020)
- Marines: United States: Window display, Circa 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1021)
- Marker: Destruction Island, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1025)
- Marker: Roadside: Waiilatpu, 1951 April (Box 3, Folder 1026)
- Marsh, 1949 January 12 (Box 3, Folder 1027)
- Marshall Funeral Home: Casket picture of J.D. Holliday, 1950 August 10 (Box 3, Folder 1028)
- Marsolek, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1029)
- Marsolek, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1030)
- Marsolek: Floods, 1941 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 1031)
- Martin, Avonelli: Alpha Ti, 1948 November 19 (Box 3, Folder 1033)
- Martin, Clarence, 1941 December (Box 3, Folder 1034)
- Martin, Hattie C., 1947 October 25 (Box 3, Folder 1035)
- Martin, Miss: Starbuck, Washington, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1036)
- Martin: Asa, May: Female friend, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1525)
- Martin: Asa, May: Husband, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1524)
- Martin: Asa, May: Short man (Corporal Julius), Undated (Box 4, Folder 1526)
- Martin: Mess tent: World War I, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1032)
- Maryhill, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1037)
- Maryhill Museum: Columbia River, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1038)
- Mason, Charles: Family group, 1948 November 6 (Box 3, Folder 1039)
- Mathews, Harry and wife: American United shows, 1944 September (Box 3, Folder 1042)
- Matthews, Beatrice, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1041)
- Mature, Victor, 1945 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 1040)
- Maxine, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1043)
- Maxson, 1951 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 1045)
- Maxson, Howard Street Grocery: Store interior, 1949 May 27 (Box 3, Folder 1044)
- McCallum Auto, 1946 October 27 (Box 3, Folder 992)
- McCallum Pontiac Company Building, Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
- McCarrol, Deloris, 1948 January (Box 3, Folder 961)
- McCarrol, Joyce, 1947 December 2 (Box 3, Folder 962)
- McCarrol, Miss: Portrait, 1950 February 7 (Box 3, Folder 963)
- McCarrol: Identification photos, 1950 June 14 (Box 3, Folder 960)
- McCarty, Doctor, Undated (Box 3, Folder 964)
- McCarty, John and family, Undated (Box 3, Folder 965)
- McCaslin, Sergeant Al, Undated (Box 3, Folder 966)
- McCauley family reunion: Lewis and Clark Park, 1950 June 11 (Box 3, Folder 959)
- McCaw dance: Pet party, Non Commissioned Officers party, 1945 June 9 (Box 3, Folder 971)
- McCaw Hospital, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- McCaw Hospital: Artist patient, Undated (Box 2, Folder 758)
- McCaw Hospital: Boiler men, Undated (Box 2, Folder 759)
- McCaw Hospital: Bond drive, 1944 June (Box 2, Folder 760)
- McCaw Hospital: Clerical mess number 1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 761)
- McCaw Hospital: Club: Non Commissioned Officers: Marriage engagements dinner, 1944 September 23 (Box 2, Folder 762)
- McCaw Hospital: Electricians and plumbers, 1944 July 6 (Box 2, Folder 764)
- McCaw Hospital: Eustis, Dorothy: Pianist, 1944 June 22 (Box 2, Folder 765)
- McCaw Hospital: Exhibit b at military show, 1943 December (Box 2, Folder 766)
- McCaw Hospital: Fire department, Undated (Box 2, Folder 767)
- McCaw Hospital: Fire department, 1944 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 768)
- McCaw Hospital: Froneis, Kay, Undated (Box 2, Folder 771)
- McCaw Hospital: Gaines, Colonel, 1944 June (Box 2, Folder 763)
- McCaw Hospital: General, 1944 June 13 (Box 2, Folder 769)
- McCaw Hospital: Lab Personnel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 775)
- McCaw Hospital: Last group leaving: N. P. Depot, 1946 February 6 (Box 2, Folder 772)
- McCaw Hospital: Laundry, 1944 July 5 (Box 2, Folder 773)
- McCaw Hospital: Longlie, Governor, 1944 June (Box 2, Folder 770)
- McCaw Hospital: McCracken; Corporal Stephen Henry: Officer candidate school candidates, Undated (Box 2, Folder 776)
- McCaw Hospital: Mess Number 1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 778)
- McCaw Hospital: Mess Number 2, 1944 July 5 (Box 2, Folder 779)
- McCaw Hospital: Mess Officers, 1944 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 777)
- McCaw Hospital: Non Commissioned Officers Club: Halloween Party, Circa 1944 (Box 2, Folder 774)
- McCaw Hospital: Non Commissioned Officers Club: Turkey raffle, 44153 (Box 2, Folder 780)
- McCaw Hospital: Occupational therapy, 1944 June (Box 2, Folder 781)
- McCaw Hospital: Orthopedic staff, Undated (Box 2, Folder 782)
- McCaw Hospital: Playing horseshoes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 783)
- McCaw Hospital: Q.M. Department, Undated (Box 2, Folder 784)
- McCaw Hospital: Softball team, 1944 July (Box 2, Folder 785)
- McCaw Hospital: Special service office, Undated (Box 2, Folder 786)
- McCaw Hospital: Walla Walla, Undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
- McCaw, Allen Opal, Undated (Box 3, Folder 967)
- McCaw, Central Service, 1945 November (Box 3, Folder 969)
- McCaw: Avalon F.A. and W.W.: Last Non Commissioned Officer party, Undated (Box 3, Folder 968)
- McCaw: Dental clinic, 1945 September 1 (Box 3, Folder 972)
- McCaw: Gabriel, Corporal Frank E: Father of 8 children.;Sergeant Charles E. Knapp, Undated (Box 3, Folder 970)
- McCaw: Guard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 975)
- McCaw: Halloween party: Non Commissioned Officers, Circa 1945 (Box 3, Folder 976)
- McCaw: Hospital Military Personnel Department, 1945 August 31 (Box 3, Folder 977)
- McCaw: Hospital: Restricted, Undated (Box 3, Folder 979)
- McCaw: Hospital: Veyette, Q.M., Undated (Box 3, Folder 978)
- McCaw: Lieutenant Kryzwicki: Q.M., Undated (Box 3, Folder 980)
- McCaw: Lieutenant Sanford: Laundry, Undated (Box 3, Folder 981)
- McCaw: Mess, Undated (Box 3, Folder 973)
- McCaw: Microscope, 1945 August 31 (Box 3, Folder 982)
- McCaw: Non Commissioned Officers, 1945 November 24 (Box 3, Folder 984)
- McCaw: Non Commissioned Officers: Sergeant Clay party, 1945 November 24 (Box 3, Folder 983)
- McCaw: Party, 1945 November 10 (Box 3, Folder 974)
- McCaw: Q.M. Officers, 1945 November (Box 3, Folder 985)
- McCaw: Sergeant Spehro, Q.M., Undated (Box 3, Folder 986)
- McCaw: W.A.C, 1945 November (Box 3, Folder 988)
- McCaw: W.A.C: Veyette and Allen, Q.M., Undated (Box 3, Folder 989)
- McCaw: X -ray: Schlosser, Undated (Box 3, Folder 987)
- McClinton, Mary, 1947 December 9 (Box 3, Folder 990)
- McClure, Sergeant: Clinical lab, McCaw Hospital, 1944 November 29 (Box 3, Folder 991)
- McDonald, Shirley, 1947 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 993)
- McFall: Starfield Rodeo, 1944 May (Box 3, Folder 994)
- McGinnis: Fiftieth Wedding anniversary: YWCA, 1945 July 1 (Box 3, Folder 995)
- McIver, Donna: Telephone office, 1947 December 13 (Box 3, Folder 996)
- McKenzie Pass, Oregon, Circa 1952 (Box 3, Folder 997)
- McMurdo, Mrs., 1949 September (Box 3, Folder 998)
- McMurty and Smith: Lyman Hall: Whitman College, Undated (Box 3, Folder 999)
- McNary Dam, Circa 1954 (Box 3, Folder 1000)
- McNary Dam Site, Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
- McNicholas, baby, 1946 October 26 (Box 3, Folder 1001)
- McNichols, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1002)
- McVay, Al, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1003)
- Mead, R.E., 1947 September 28 (Box 3, Folder 1046)
- Menken, Arthur: Internationally famous war correspondent, 1942 March (Box 3, Folder 1047)
- Mertin: Julius, Corporal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1527)
- Metropolitan store: Dayton, 1948 June 17 (Box 3, Folder 1048)
- Miler: Anderson, Grocery, Circa 1947 (Box 3, Folder 1051)
- Military, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1049)
- Mill Creek Paving, 1948 October (Box 3, Folder 1050A)
- Mill, paper: Shelton, Washington, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1050)
- Miller, 1946 October 10 (Box 3, Folder 1053)
- Miller, Colonel: Speaking at C.W. Def meeting, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1054)
- Miller, Fred, 1950 April (Box 3, Folder 1057)
- Miller, Fred: Anderson Grocery, 1950 April 8 (Box 3, Folder 1056)
- Miller, Fred: With pal: Enlisted Army, 1942 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 1055)
- Miller: Anderson Grocery, 1948 April 7 (Box 3, Folder 1052)
- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous [Group photographs], Undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1059)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Agriculture, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.01)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Airplane, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.11)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Buildings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.03)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Cars, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.08)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Cemetery, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.05)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: People, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.04)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Soda fountain, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.06)
- Miscellaneous negatives: Old: Swimming Pool, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1060.1)